oswfs.com 2016-05-21

# Privacy Policy

Effective date: December 1 2015

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”), applies to all subsidiaries owned and operated by Small World Financial Services Group Limited (“SWFS”, “We”, “Us”, “Our”).  Please click this link to access the list of our subsidiaries in the EU*. This Policy describes how We collect and use the Personal Data you provide on our website www.smallworldfs.com. This Policy also applies for the Personal Data collected offline. The Policy describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Data and how you can access and update this data.   
Personal Data is data which can identify you, directly or indirectly, either from that data or from that data combined with other information that is in, or likely to come into, our possession, it includes data such as your name, your location or online identifiers.  By submitting your Personal Data to us you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Policy.

SCOPE OF PRIVACY POLICY

This Policy applies to Personal Data collected by us in connection with services we offer.  This Policy applies to Personal Data we may collect via electronic channels and in hard copies (for example letters you post to us).  
Our website may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates (for example Google, Twitter).  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any Personal Data to these websites.

DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

We collect Personal Data which you disclosure to us via online and offline means:  
•    We collect your Personal Data and Personal Data of your beneficiaries when you create money transfer account with us by completing online forms.  Personal Data we collect about you may include: name, surname, home address, email address, date of birth, mobile number, email address, credit, financial information and other Personal Data which is required to complete the transaction.  
•    We do not knowingly collect and process sensitive Personal Data such as Personal Data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinion, religious philosophical beliefs, trade union membership and data concerning health and sex life.  
Technical data   
•    We may collect technical information about your visit such as Internet Protocol Address (IP); clickstreams to, through and from our website (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors; length of visits to certain pages; page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs); your login information, browser type and version; time zone setting; browser plug-in types and versions; operating system and platform and etc.

PURPOSES WE USE YOUR DATA  
Personal Data held about you will be used for our core business and marketing purposes such as follows:   
•    to facilitate your monetary transaction;  
•    to respond to any queries or provide you with information, products or services that you request;  
•    to prevent or detect fraud, including fraudulent transactions, or abuses of our Website;  
•    to ensure that content from our website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;  
•    to administer our website and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;  
•    as part of our efforts to keep our website safe and secure;  
•    to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;  
•    to manage our account and records;  
•    to conduct research and analysis; and   
•    to comply with applicable law, regulations and court orders.

INFORMATION SHARING   
We may provide your Personal Data to trusted third parties who help us with our business activities such as processing your monetary transaction or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your Personal Data only as necessary to provide these services to us. We may also disclose your Personal Data:  
•    in the event of a  merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we will share your Personal Data with our successor;    
•    with analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our website;  
•    to any other third party with your prior consent to do so; and  
•    if we are under a duty to disclose or share your Personal Data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Website Terms of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or protect our safety, our members, or others.  This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

YOUR RIGHTS

Data protection law gives rights to individuals in respect of the Personal Data that organisations collect and hold about them: for example you have the right to ask us not to process your Personal Data for marketing purposes. If your Personal Data changes or if you no longer desire our service, you may exercise his/her rights to access, correct, modify, delete or cancel his/her account, by making the change on the member information page or by e-mail to the following address: info@smallworldfs.com. You may also call us on our customer service number at +44 800 019 5030. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.  
Receiving emails from us is part of our service. You will only receive service related email from us in order for us to manage and administer your account.

TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA   
We are a global company; your Personal Data may be transferred outside of the country in which you live. All international transfers of Personal Data are done in accordance with applicable data protection laws for the purposes set out in this Policy.   
SECURITY   
We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy. We implement technical and organisation measures to protect your Personal Data and follow data retention practises in line with applicable law. .  
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES  
Our website includes links to other sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of SWFS. If you submit Personal Data to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any site you visit.  
TESTIMONIALS  
We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at info@smallworldfs.com.  
REFERRALS  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the website. SWFS stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at info@smallworldfs.com to request that we remove this information from our database.  
COLLECTION AND USE OF THIRD PARTY PERSONAL DATA  
You may also provide Personal Data about other people, such as their name, email address, beneficiary account number and mobile number. This information is only used for the sole purpose of adding a new beneficiary to send money to.  
SOCIAL MEDIA WIDGETS  
Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. Please refer to our Cookie Policy to obtain more information about cookies we use.  
CHANGES TO THIS POLICY  
Any changes we may make to Policy in the future will be posted on this page, and where appropriate notified to you by email.  We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.  
CONTACT US  
If you have questions or concerns about this Policy, please contact us by email:   
info@smallworldfs.com  
Or sending us a letter:  
Small World Financial Services Group Limited Units 3 & 4 Sycamore Court Royal Oak Yard  
168-170 Bermondsey Street London SE1 3TQ  
England

*Belgium - LCC Trans - Envoi SPRL  
  Bulgaria - Choice Bulgaria Limited  
  Portugal - LCC Transferencia De Dinheiro, Unipessoal LDA  
  Spain - Small World Exchange Services, Spain SLU  
  Spain - Small World Financial Services Spain, SAU   
  Sweden - Small World Financial Services Sweden AB   
  Switzerland Swiss Transfers GmbH  
  Norway - Small World Financial Services Norway AS   
  United Kingdom - Small World Card Services Limited (UK)  
  United Kingdom - LCC Trans-Sending Holdings Limited  
  United Kingdom - LCC Trans-Sending Limited (UK)
